<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>org.kde.atcore.desktop</id>
  <name>AtCore Test Client</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Client de prova de l'AtCore</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">AtCore Test Client</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Cliente de prueba de AtCore</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">AtCore testclient</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Тестовий клієнт AtCore</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxAtCore Test Clientxx</name>
  <summary>A test application for the AtCore framework to control 3D printers</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Una aplicació de prova per a l'entorn de treball AtCore per controlar impressores 3D</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">A test application for the AtCore framework to control 3D printers</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Una aplicación de pruebas para la infraestructura AtCore de control de impresoras en 3D</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Een testtoepassing voor het AtCore-framework om 3D-printers te besturen</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Тестова програма для бібліотек AtCore, які призначено для керування 3D-принтерами</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxA test application for the AtCore framework to control 3D printersxx</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
        AtCore is the API that controls the 3DPrinter and its basic functionalities. AtCore comes with a test client called atcore-gui to manage your printer.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">L'AtCore és l'API que controla la impressora 3D i les seves funcionalitats bàsiques. L'AtCore ve amb client de prova anomenant «atcore-gui» per gestionar la impressora.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">AtCore is the API that controls the 3DPrinter and its basic functionalities. AtCore comes with a test client called atcore-gui to manage your printer.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">AtCore es la API que controla la impresión en 3D y sus funcionalidades básicas. AtCore contiene una aplicación cliente de pruebas llamada «atcore-gui» para gestionar la impresora.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">AtCore is de API die de 3D-printer en zijn basis functionaliteiten bestuurt. AtCore komt met een testclient genaamd atcore-gui om uw printer te beheren.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">AtCore — програмний інтерфейс для керування 3D-принтером та його базовими можливостями. AtCore постачається із тестовим клієнтом із назвою atcore-gui, за допомогою якого можна керувати вашим принтером.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxAtCore is the API that controls the 3DPrinter and its basic functionalities. AtCore comes with a test client called atcore-gui to manage your printer.xx</p>
    <p>
        This is an AtCore test application to showcase the framework.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Aquesta és una aplicació de prova de l'AtCore per exposar l'entorn de treball.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Dies ist eine AtCore-Testanwendung, um das Framework demonstrieren.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">This is an AtCore test application to showcase the framework.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Esto es una aplicación de pruebas de AtCore mara mostrar la infraestructura.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Dit is een AtCore testtoepassing om het framework te tonen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Це тестова програма AtCore, яка демонструє можливості бібліотеки.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxThis is an AtCore test application to showcase the framework.xx</p>
  </description>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>LGPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <url type="homepage">https://atelier.kde.org</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=atcore</url>
  <url type="help">https://atelier.kde.org/documentation/atcore</url>
  <url type="donation">https://kde.org/donate/?app=atcore</url>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
</component>
