<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
    SPDX-FileCopyrightText: none
    SPDX-License-Identifier: CC0-1.0
-->
<component type="desktop">
  <id>org.kde.atcore.desktop</id>
  <name>AtCore Test Client</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Client de prova de l'AtCore</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">Client de prova d'AtCore</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Testovací klient AtCore</name>
  <name xml:lang="da">AtCore-testklient</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">AtCore-Testprogramm</name>
  <name xml:lang="el">Πελάτης δοκιμών AtCore</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">AtCore Test Client</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Cliente de prueba de AtCore</name>
  <name xml:lang="et">AtCore testklient</name>
  <name xml:lang="eu">AtCore probatzeko bezeroa</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">AtCore-koeasiakas</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">Client de test « AtCore »</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">Cliente de probas de AtCore</name>
  <name xml:lang="hi">AtCore परीक्षण ग्राहक</name>
  <name xml:lang="ia">Cliente de prova de AtCore</name>
  <name xml:lang="id">AtCore Test Client</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">Client di prova per AtCore</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">AtCore 테스트 클라이언트</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">AtCore testclient</name>
  <name xml:lang="nn">AtCore-testklient</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">AtCore - Klient próbny</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Cliente de Testes do AtCore</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">Cliente de testes AtCore</name>
  <name xml:lang="ro">Client de test AtCore</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">Тестовый клиент AtCore</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">AtCore Test Klient</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">Preizkusni odjemalec AtCore</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">AtCore testklient</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Тестовий клієнт AtCore</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxAtCore Test Clientxx</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-CN">AtCore 测试客户端</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-TW">AtCore 測試用戶端</name>
  <summary>A test application for the AtCore framework to control 3D printers</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Una aplicació de prova per a l'entorn de treball AtCore per a controlar les impressores 3D</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Una aplicació de prova per a l'entorn de treball AtCore per a controlar les impressores 3D</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Testovací aplikace pro framework AtCore pro ovládání 3D tiskáren</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Ein Testprogramm für die AtCore-Bibliothek zur Steuerung von 3D-Druckern</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="el">Μια δοκιμαστική εφαρμογή για το AtCore για τον έλεγχο τρισδιάστατων εκτυπωτών</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">A test application for the AtCore framework to control 3D printers</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Una aplicación de pruebas para la infraestructura AtCore de control de impresoras en 3D</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="et">3D-printerite juhtimiseks mõeldud AtCore raamistiku testrakendus</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eu">3D inprimagailuak kontrolatzeko AtCore azpiegitura probatzeko aplikazio bat</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">Koeasiakas 3D-tulostinten AtCore-hallintakehykseen</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Une application de test pour l'environnement « AtCore » permettant de contrôler les imprimantes 3D.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">Unha aplicación de probas para a infraestrutura AtCore para controlar impresoras 3D</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hi">AtCore तंत्र 3D प्रिंटर को नियंत्रित करने के लिए एक परीक्षण अनुप्रयोग है</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="id">Sebuah aplikasi uji untuk kerangka kerja AtCore guna mengendalikan printer 3D</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Un'applicazione di prova per il framework AtCore, che controlla le stampanti 3D</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ko">3D 프린터를 제어하는 AtCore 프레임워크 테스트 프로그램</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Een testtoepassing voor het AtCore-framework om 3D-printers te besturen</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nn">Eit testprogram for AtCore-rammeverket for kontrollering av 3D-skrivarar</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Aplikacja próbna dla szkieletu AtCore do sterowania drukarkami 3D</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Uma aplicação de testes da plataforma AtCore para controlar as impressoras 3D</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">Um aplicativo de teste para o framework do AtCore para controlar impressoras 3D</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ro">Aplicație de probă pentru platforma AtCore pentru a controla imprimante 3D</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Preskusna aplikacija za ogrodje AtCore za nadzor 3D-tiskalnikov</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Ett testprogram av ramverket AtCore för att styra 3D-skrivare</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Тестова програма для бібліотек AtCore, які призначено для керування 3D-принтерами</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxA test application for the AtCore framework to control 3D printersxx</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-CN">一个测试应用程序，用于控制 3D 打印机的 AtCore 框架</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-TW">一個用來讓 AtCore 框架控制 3D 列印機的測試應用程式</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
        AtCore is the API that controls the 3DPrinter and its basic functionalities. AtCore comes with a test client called atcore-gui to manage your printer.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">L'AtCore és l'API que controla la impressora 3D i les seves funcionalitats bàsiques. L'AtCore ve amb client de prova anomenant «atcore-gui» per a gestionar la impressora.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">AtCore és l'API que controla la impressora 3D i les seues funcionalitats bàsiques. AtCore ve amb client de prova anomenant «atcore-gui» per a gestionar la impressora.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">AtCore ist die API, die den 3DDrucker und seine grundlegenden Funktionalitäten steuert. AtCore wird mit einem Test-Programm namens atcore-gui geliefert, um Ihren Drucker zu verwalten.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Το AtCore είναι το API που ελέγχει τον 3D εκτυπωτή και τις βασικές λειτουργίες του. Το AtCore συνοδεύεται από έναν πελάτη δοκιμών που ονομάζεται atcore-gui για τη διαχείριση του εκτυπωτή.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">AtCore is the API that controls the 3DPrinter and its basic functionalities. AtCore comes with a test client called atcore-gui to manage your printer.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">AtCore es la API que controla la impresión en 3D y sus funcionalidades básicas. AtCore contiene una aplicación cliente de pruebas llamada «atcore-gui» para gestionar la impresora.</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">AtCore kujutab endast API-t, mis võimaldab juhtida 3D-printereid ja nende põhifunktsioone. AtCore pakub testklienti atcore-gui 3D-printeri haldamiseks.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">AtCore da 3D inprimagailua eta bere oinarrizko funtzionaltasunak kontrolatzen dituen API-a. AtCore zure inprimagailua kudeatzeko atcore-gui izeneko probako aplikazio batekin dator.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">AtCore on API, joka hallitsee 3D-tulostimen perustoimintoja. AtCoren mukana tulee koeasiakas nimeltä atcore-gui, jolla voit hallita tulostintasi.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">AtCore est l'API qui contrôle l'imprimante 3D et ses fonctionnalités de base. AtCore est accompagné d'un client de test appelé atcore-gui pour gérer votre imprimante.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">AtCore é a API que controla a impresora 3D e as súas funcionalidades básicas. AtCore inclúe un cliente de probas chamado atcore-gui para xestionar a súa impresora.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hi">AtCore एक एपीआई है जो 3D प्रिंटर की नियंत्रित करता व मुल क्रियाएँ को देखता है. AtCore के साथ atcore-gui परीक्षण अनुप्रयोग आता है जो आपके प्रिंटर को चलाता है</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">AtCore adalah API yang mengendalikan 3DPrinter dan yang berbasiskan fungsionalitas. AtCore hadir dengan sebuah klien uji yang disebut atcore-gui untuk mengelola printer-mu.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">AtCore è l'API che controlla la stampante 3D e le sue funzionalità di base. Viene fornito con un client di prova chiamato atcore-gui che gestisce la tua stampante.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">AtCore는 3D 프린터와 기본 기능을 제어하는 API입니다. 프린터를 관리할 수 있는 atcore-gui 테스트 클라이언트가 같이 제공됩니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">AtCore is de API die de 3D-printer en zijn basis functionaliteiten bestuurt. AtCore komt met een testclient genaamd atcore-gui om uw printer te beheren.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nn">AtCore er API-et som kontrollerer dei grunnleggjande funksjonane til 3D-skrivaren. Det følgjer ein testklient, «atcore-gui», med AtCore, som du kan bruka til å styra skrivaren.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">AtCore jest API do sterowania drukarkami 3D i ich podstawowymi możliwościami. AtCore jest dostarczany z klientem próbnym o nazwie atcore-gui do zarządzania twoją drukarką.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O AtCore é a API que controla as impressoras 3D e a suas funcionalidades básicas. O AtCore vem com um cliente de testes chamado 'atcore-gui' para gerir a sua impressora.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">AtCore é a API que controla o 3DPrinter e suas funcionalidades básicas. Vem com um cliente de teste chamado atcore-gui para gerenciar sua impressora.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ro">AtCore este un API ce controlează imprimanta 3D și funcționalitățile sale de bază. AtCore vine cu un client de probă denumit atcore-gui pentru a vă gestiona imprimanta.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">AtCore je API, ki nadzoruje 3Dtiskalnik in njegove osnovne funkcije.AtCore vključuje tudi s testnega odjemalca atcore-gui za upravljanje tiskalnika.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">AtCore är programmeringsgränssnittet som styr 3D-skrivaren och dess grundfunktioner. AtCore levereras med en testklient som kallas atcore-gui för att hantera skrivaren.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">AtCore — програмний інтерфейс для керування 3D-принтером та його базовими можливостями. AtCore постачається із тестовим клієнтом із назвою atcore-gui, за допомогою якого можна керувати вашим принтером.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxAtCore is the API that controls the 3DPrinter and its basic functionalities. AtCore comes with a test client called atcore-gui to manage your printer.xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-CN">AtCore 是用于控制 3D 打印机及它基础功能的 API。AtCore 包含一个用于管里您的打印机的测试客户端，叫做 atcore-gui。</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-TW">AtCore 是個控制 3D 列印機及其基本功能的 API。AtCore 包含了一個叫做 atcore-gui 的測試用戶端，以管理您的列印機。</p>
    <p>
        This is an AtCore test application to showcase the framework.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Aquesta és una aplicació de prova de l'AtCore per a exposar l'entorn de treball.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Esta és una aplicació de prova d'AtCore per a exposar l'entorn de treball.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Dies ist eine AtCore-Testanwendung, um das Framework demonstrieren.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Αυτή είναι μια εφαρμογή δοκιμών του AtCore για την παρουσίαση του πλαισίου.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">This is an AtCore test application to showcase the framework.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Esto es una aplicación de pruebas de AtCore mara mostrar la infraestructura.</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">AtCore testrakendus raamistikku esitlemas.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Azpiegituraren erakustaldia egiteko AtCore-ren probako aplikazio bat da hau.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Tämä on kehyksen esittelyyn tarkoitettu AtCore-koeasiakas.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Ceci est une application de test « AtCore » permettant de tester les fonctionnalités de l'environnement.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Isto é unha aplicación de probas de AtCore para demostrar a infraestrutura.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hi">यह एक AtCore परीक्षण अनुप्रयोग है, जो तंत्र को दर्शाता है</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Ini adalah sebuah aplikasi uji AtCore untuk menampilkan kerangka kerja.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Questa è un'applicazione di prova per mettere in mostra il framework.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">AtCore 프레임워크의 기능을 보여 주는 테스트 프로그램입니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Dit is een AtCore testtoepassing om het framework te tonen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nn">Dette er eit testprogram for AtCore, for å visa fram rammeverket.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Oto aplikacja próbna AtCore do przedstawienia szkieletu.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Esta é uma aplicação de testes do AtCore para demonstrar a plataforma.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Este é um aplicativo de teste AtCore para demonstrar o framework.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ro">Aceasta e o aplicație de probă AtCore pentru a demonstra platforma.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">To je preizkusna aplikacija AtCore, ki prikazuje programsko ogrodje.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Det här är ett testprogram för AtCore för att visa upp ramverket</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Це тестова програма AtCore, яка демонструє можливості бібліотеки.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxThis is an AtCore test application to showcase the framework.xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-CN">这是用于展示这个框架的 AtCore 测试引用程序。</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-TW">此為用來展示框架的 AtCore 測試應用程式。</p>
  </description>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0+</project_license>
  <url type="homepage">https://atelier.kde.org</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?product=Atelier&amp;component=AtCore</url>
  <url type="help">https://atelier.kde.org/documentation/atcore</url>
  <url type="donation">https://kde.org/donate/?app=atcore</url>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
</component>
